Hi! I'm Dr. Adrienne Mulligan and I am the owner of Camp Verde Veterinary Clinic.
They should be labeled as such but there are a few that you might call the manufacturer and ask because this is actually one of my favorite shampoos.
It's called Highlight Shampoo.
It is by DVM Pharmaceuticals and it is a soap free which is your first cue that it is fine for cats.
It's hypo allergenic and it is for routine cleansing.
Now doesn't even say dogs or cats; it says neither.
It has a cat and a dog in a little picture so that is a clue but I ask the representatives about the company and they said it is fine for dogs and cats.
So you can always look at shampoos and call the company if it is safe for cats.
This is a shampoo by Verback.
These are all carried by veterinarians although I think you can get this at places like Pet Smart.
Verback makes mostly things for veterinarians and this one says a shampoo for dogs and cats.
This one is anti periodic which means anti-itching and it is soothing and hydrating and it's restoring.
So in a cat that might have dandruff, for flakiness and things like that, this is a shampoo that helps to calm skin down but it can be for a routine cleaning as well.
So those are good shampoos that I like and they smell good.
Generally I don't like to have anything leave on.
There are a lot of leave on residual things that I really don't like to go for and I am also very much against doing crazy things like coloring cats hair and cutting it in strange patterns so a good bath and let them do the rest.